{
  "category": "random",
  "questions":[
    {
      "question": "What state is round in one side , high in the middle and round on the other side?",
      "answer":   "A: Ohio",
      "optionA":  "A: Ohio",
      "optionB":  "B: Nigeria",
      "optionC":  "C: Ondo",
      "optionD":  "D: California"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the physical phase of life called?",
      "answer":   "A: Protoplasm",
      "optionA":  "A: Protoplasm",
      "optionB":  "B: Cytoplasm",
      "optionC":  "C: Organelles",
      "optionD":  "D: None of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "2010 Commonwealth Games held in ?",
      "answer":   "B: India",
      "optionA":  "A: Canada",
      "optionB":  "B: India",
      "optionC":  "C: Britian",
      "optionD":  "D: Malaysia"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which decade was the American Institute of Electrical Engineers (AIEE) founded?",
      "answer":   "B: 1880s",
      "optionA":  "A: 1850s",
      "optionB":  "B: 1880s",
      "optionC":  "C: 1930s",
      "optionD":  "D: 1950s"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first name of Russia's President Putin?",
      "answer":   "C: Vladimir",
      "optionA":  "A: Valentin",
      "optionB":  "B: Valeriy",
      "optionC":  "C: Vladimir",
      "optionD":  "D: Vladivar"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Homolographic projection has the correct representation of",
      "answer":   "B: area",
      "optionA":  "A: shape",
      "optionB":  "B: area",
      "optionC":  "C: baring",
      "optionD":  "D: distance"
    },
    {
      "question": "The god Quetzalcoatl is recognized in",
      "answer":   "D: Aztec religion",
      "optionA":  "A: Cherokee religion",
      "optionB":  "B: All Native American religions",
      "optionC":  "C: Modoc religion",
      "optionD":  "D: Aztec religion"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am found at the beginning of time. What am I?",
      "answer":   "B: T",
      "optionA":  "A: Nothing",
      "optionB":  "B: T",
      "optionC":  "C: 0",
      "optionD":  "D: 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The largest cell is ________________",
      "answer":   "C: The egg of an Ostrich",
      "optionA":  "A: Nerve Cell",
      "optionB":  "B: Ovum",
      "optionC":  "C: The egg of an Ostrich",
      "optionD":  "D: None of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "The term“Googly” is associated with ?",
      "answer":   "A: Cricket",
      "optionA":  "A: Cricket",
      "optionB":  "B: Football",
      "optionC":  "C: Badminton",
      "optionD":  "D: Hockey"
    },

    {
      "question": "What is found at the center of the earth?",
      "answer":   "B: r",
      "optionA":  "A: Gravity",
      "optionB":  "B: r",
      "optionC":  "C: Alphabet",
      "optionD":  "D: e"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the largest human cell?",
      "answer":   "D: Ovum",
      "optionA":  "A: Liver",
      "optionB":  "B: Skin",
      "optionC":  "C: Spleen",
      "optionD":  "D: Ovum"
    },
    {
      "question": "Aga Khan Cup is awarded to ?",
      "answer":   "C: National Hockey in India",
      "optionA":  "A: International Hockey",
      "optionB":  "B: Asian Hockey",
      "optionC":  "C: National Hockey in India",
      "optionD":  "D: None of these"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is part of a database that holds only one type of information?",
      "answer":   "B: Field",
      "optionA":  "A: Report",
      "optionB":  "B: Field",
      "optionC":  "C: Record",
      "optionD":  "D: File"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which one of the following is not related to disarmament?",
      "answer":   "D: NATO",
      "optionA":  "A: SALT",
      "optionB":  "B: NPT",
      "optionC":  "C: CTBT",
      "optionD":  "D: NATO"
    },
    {
      "question": "The latitudinal differences in pressure delineate a number of major pressure zones, which correspond with",
      "answer":   "A: zones of climate",
      "optionA":  "A: zones of climate",
      "optionB":  "B: zones of oceans",
      "optionC":  "C: zones of land",
      "optionD":  "D: zones of cyclonic depressions"
    },
    {
      "question": "The higher the wind speed and the longer the fetch or distance of open water across which the wind blows and waves travel, the ____ waves and the ____ energy they process.",
      "answer":   "A: larger, more",
      "optionA":  "A: larger, more",
      "optionB":  "B: larger, less",
      "optionC":  "C: smaller, more",
      "optionD":  "D: smaller, less"
    },
    {
      "question": "The ancestral spirits of the Pueblo peoples are known as",
      "answer":   "B: Kachinas",
      "optionA":  "A: The Hero Twins",
      "optionB":  "B: Kachinas",
      "optionC":  "C: Jump Dancers",
      "optionD":  "D: None of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has ring but no finger?",
      "answer":   "B: telephone",
      "optionA":  "A: Ring",
      "optionB":  "B: telephone",
      "optionC":  "C: clock",
      "optionD":  "D: Nothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "_________________ is the longest cell.",
      "answer":   "A: Nerve Cell",
      "optionA":  "A: Nerve Cell",
      "optionB":  "B: Skin",
      "optionC":  "C: Spleen",
      "optionD":  "D: None of the above"
    },

    {
      "question": "Krishna Poonia is associated with ?",
      "answer":   "C: Chess",
      "optionA":  "A: Football",
      "optionB":  "B: Hockey",
      "optionC":  "C: Chess",
      "optionD":  "D: Athletics"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whom is the Queen's representative in Australia?",
      "answer":   "A: Governor-General",
      "optionA":  "A: Governor-General",
      "optionB":  "B: President",
      "optionC":  "C: Prime Minister",
      "optionD":  "D: Prince of New South Wales"
    },
    {
      "question": "The hazards of radiation belts include",
      "answer":   "D: All of the above",
      "optionA":  "A: deterioration of electronic circuits",
      "optionB":  "B: damage of solar cells of spacecraft",
      "optionC":  "C: adverse effect on living organisms",
      "optionD":  "D: All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "The cycle of birth, death and rebirth. You pay for good or bad deeds based on your behavior.",
      "answer":   "B: reincarnation",
      "optionA":  "A: karma",
      "optionB":  "B: reincarnation",
      "optionC":  "C: Hinduism",
      "optionD":  "D: caste system"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is as big as the elephant but weighs 0 kg? It is the elephant's....",
      "answer":   "C: Shadow",
      "optionA":  "A: Tail",
      "optionB":  "B: Bone",
      "optionC":  "C: Shadow",
      "optionD":  "D: Eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the cells in the body that engulf foreign particles like bacteria?",
      "answer":   "A: Phagocytes",
      "optionA":  "A: Phagocytes",
      "optionB":  "B: Globulin",
      "optionC":  "C: Fibrinogen",
      "optionD":  "D: Albumin"
    },
    {
      "question": "In 1924 the first winter Olympics was held in ?",
      "answer":   "B: France",
      "optionA":  "A: Italy",
      "optionB":  "B: France",
      "optionC":  "C: Austria",
      "optionD":  "D: Canada"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which decade with the first transatlantic radio broadcast occur?",
      "answer":   "D: 1900s",
      "optionA":  "A: 1850s",
      "optionB":  "B: 1860s",
      "optionC":  "C: 1870s",
      "optionD":  "D: 1900s"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whom did George W. Bush defeat in the elections of November 2004?",
      "answer":   "C: John Kerry",
      "optionA":  "A: Al Gore",
      "optionB":  "B: Arnold Schwarzenegger",
      "optionC":  "C: John Kerry",
      "optionD":  "D: Rudy Giuliani"
    },
    {
      "question": "The great Victoria Desert is located in",
      "answer":   "C: Australia",
      "optionA":  "A: Canada",
      "optionB":  "B: West Africa",
      "optionC":  "C: Australia",
      "optionD":  "D: North America"
    },

    {
      "question": "Judaism, Christianity, and Islam all ____________________________.",
      "answer":   "C: Worship only one God",
      "optionA":  "A: Believe in many divine Gods",
      "optionB":  "B: Worship only one God",
      "optionC":  "C: Follow the teachings of the Qu'ran",
      "optionD":  "D: Believe Jesus was the son of God"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Torah is the sacred writing (holy book) for which religion?",
      "answer":   "A: Judaism",
      "optionA":  "A: Judaism",
      "optionB":  "B: Christianity",
      "optionC":  "C: Islam",
      "optionD":  "D: None"
    },
    {
      "question": "The belief that the soul never dies but is continually reborn or reincarnated is associated with which religion?",
      "answer":   "D: Hinduism and Buddhism",
      "optionA":  "A: Islam",
      "optionB":  "B: Christianity",
      "optionC":  "C: Judaism",
      "optionD":  "D: Hinduism and Buddhism"
    },
    {
      "question": "Following the Eightfold Path and the Four Noble Truths to achieve enlightenment is associated with which religion?",
      "answer":   "A: Buddhism",
      "optionA":  "A: Buddhism",
      "optionB":  "B: Hinduism",
      "optionC":  "C: Islam",
      "optionD":  "D: Christianity"
    },
    {
      "question": "This religion can be divided into Catholic, Protestant, and Orthodox sects.",
      "answer":   "B: Christianity",
      "optionA":  "A: Judaism",
      "optionB":  "B: Christianity",
      "optionC":  "C: Islam",
      "optionD":  "D: Buddhism"
    },
    {
      "question": "Diwali, the festival of Lights is important to which religion?",
      "answer":   "D: Hinduism",
      "optionA":  "A: Judaism",
      "optionB":  "B: Christianity",
      "optionC":  "C: Islam",
      "optionD":  "D: Hinduism"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ramadan is the holy month of fasting for which religion?",
      "answer":   "C: Islam",
      "optionA":  "A: Judaism",
      "optionB":  "B: Christianity",
      "optionC":  "C: Islam",
      "optionD":  "D: Hinduism"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do Sikhs treat their women?",
      "answer":   "A: With respect, dignity and equality",
      "optionA":  "A: With respect, dignity and equality",
      "optionB":  "B: Like inferiors",
      "optionC":  "C: Harshly, beating and verbally abusing them",
      "optionD":  "D: They make them wear veils and be secluded"
    },
    {
      "question": "The clergy for Christianity are called _______________.",
      "answer":   "B: Priests or ministers",
      "optionA":  "A: Rabbis",
      "optionB":  "B: Priests or ministers",
      "optionC":  "C: Imams",
      "optionD":  "D: Brahman"
    },
    {
      "question": "The clergy for Judaism are called _________________.",
      "answer":   "C: Rabbis",
      "optionA":  "A: Monks",
      "optionB":  "B: Priests",
      "optionC":  "C: Rabbis",
      "optionD":  "D: Imams"
    },

    {
      "question": "Light from the nearest star reaches the earth in",
      "answer":   "C: 4.3 years",
      "optionA":  "A: 4.3 minutes",
      "optionB":  "B: 43 minutes",
      "optionC":  "C: 4.3 years",
      "optionD":  "D: 4.3 seconds"
    },
    {
      "question": "Duncan pass is located between",
      "answer":   "D: South and Little Andaman",
      "optionA":  "A: Andaman and Nicobar",
      "optionB":  "B: North and Middle Andaman",
      "optionC":  "C: North and South Andaman",
      "optionD":  "D: South and Little Andaman"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the importance of ozone in the atmosphere?",
      "answer":   "D: it provides protection against ultraviolet radiation",
      "optionA":  "A: it helps scatter blue ligh",
      "optionB":  "B: it creates the green house effect on earth",
      "optionC":  "C: it provides condensation nuclei",
      "optionD":  "D: it provides protection against ultraviolet radiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "The International Date Line passes through",
      "answer":   "A: Bering Strait",
      "optionA":  "A: Bering Strait",
      "optionB":  "B: Malacca Strait",
      "optionC":  "C: Florida Strait",
      "optionD":  "D: Gibraltar Strait"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which soil owes its colour to oxides of iron?",
      "answer":   "A: laterite",
      "optionA":  "A: laterite",
      "optionB":  "B: black",
      "optionC":  "C: alluvial",
      "optionD":  "D: none of these"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which soil swells when wet and develops cracks when dry?",
      "answer":   "B: black",
      "optionA":  "A: red",
      "optionB":  "B: black",
      "optionC":  "C: laterite",
      "optionD":  "D: alluvial"
    },
    {
      "question": "The busiest of sea trade routes is",
      "answer":   "B: North Atlantic route",
      "optionA":  "A: South Atlantic route",
      "optionB":  "B: North Atlantic route",
      "optionC":  "C: Cape of Good Hope route",
      "optionD":  "D: Suez Canal"
    },
    {
      "question": "The difference in the duration of day and night increases as one moves from",
      "answer":   "B: equator to poles",
      "optionA":  "A: poles to equator",
      "optionB":  "B: equator to poles",
      "optionC":  "C: west to east",
      "optionD":  "D: east and west of the prime meridian"
    },
    {
      "question": "The velocity of winds is governed by",
      "answer":   "C: Pressure gradient",
      "optionA":  "A: Farrel's law",
      "optionB":  "B: Insolation",
      "optionC":  "C: Pressure gradient",
      "optionD":  "D: Rotation of earth"
    },
    {
      "question": "The sun shines vertically over the equator on",
      "answer":   "B: March 21",
      "optionA":  "A: June 21",
      "optionB":  "B: March 21",
      "optionC":  "C: December 22",
      "optionD":  "D: all days"
    },

    {
      "question": "Who led the Ulster Unionist Party between 1995 and 2005?",
      "answer":   "A: David Trimble",
      "optionA":  "A: David Trimble",
      "optionB":  "B: Ian Paisley",
      "optionC":  "C: James Molyneaux",
      "optionD":  "D: Reg Empey"
    },
    {
      "question": "Of which former Labour cabinet minister is Peter Mandelson the grandson?",
      "answer":   "C: Herbert Morrison",
      "optionA":  "A: Aneurin Bevan",
      "optionB":  "B: Ernest Bevin",
      "optionC":  "C: Herbert Morrison",
      "optionD":  "D: Hugh Dalton"
    },
    {
      "question": "How old was David Owen upon being appointed Foreign Secretary in 1977?",
      "answer":   "B: 38",
      "optionA":  "A: 35",
      "optionB":  "B: 38",
      "optionC":  "C: 40",
      "optionD":  "D: 43"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the European elections of 2004 how many MEPs did Wales return?",
      "answer":   "B: 4",
      "optionA":  "A: 3",
      "optionB":  "B: 4",
      "optionC":  "C: 5",
      "optionD":  "D: 6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who in 1990 was John Major's first Home Secretary?",
      "answer":   "A: Kenneth Baker",
      "optionA":  "A: Kenneth Baker",
      "optionB":  "B: Kenneth Clarke",
      "optionC":  "C: Michael Howard",
      "optionD":  "D: Tom King"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who succeeded David Lloyd George as Prime Minister?",
      "answer":   "A: Andrew Bonar Law",
      "optionA":  "A: Andrew Bonar Law",
      "optionB":  "B: Herbert Asquith",
      "optionC":  "C: Ramsay MacDonald",
      "optionD":  "D: Stanley Baldwin"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the House Of Commons how are MPs selected to submit Private Members' Bills?",
      "answer":   "A: Ballot",
      "optionA":  "A: Ballot",
      "optionB":  "B: Length Of Service",
      "optionC":  "C: Nomination by the Speaker",
      "optionD":  "D: Party Allocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Africa's newest country?",
      "answer":   "B: South Sudan",
      "optionA":  "A: Azania",
      "optionB":  "B: South Sudan",
      "optionC":  "C: Azawad",
      "optionD":  "D: Central African Republic"
    },
    {
      "question": "What alias did Nelson Mandela use while pretending to be a caretaker at Liliesleaf farm in Johannesburg?",
      "answer":   "A: David Motsamayi",
      "optionA":  "A: David Motsamayi",
      "optionB":  "B: The Black Pimpernel",
      "optionC":  "C: Mark Radebe",
      "optionD":  "D: Rolihlahla Ntoko"
    },
    {
      "question": "In what city is the Chinese-built headquarters of the African Union?",
      "answer":   "A: Addis Ababa",
      "optionA":  "A: Addis Ababa",
      "optionB":  "B: Lagos",
      "optionC":  "C: Ouagadougou",
      "optionD":  "D: Johannesburg"
    },

    {
      "question": "Whose trademark is the operating system UNIX?",
      "answer":   "C: BELL Laboratories",
      "optionA":  "A: Motorola",
      "optionB":  "B: Microsoft",
      "optionC":  "C: BELL Laboratories",
      "optionD":  "D: AshtonTate"
    },
    {
      "question": "The first mechanical computer designed by Charles Babbage was called?",
      "answer":   "B: Analytical Engine",
      "optionA":  "A: Abacus",
      "optionB":  "B: Analytical Engine",
      "optionC":  "C: Calculator",
      "optionD":  "D: Processor"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is the most powerful type of computer?",
      "answer":   "C: Super computer",
      "optionA":  "A: Super–micro",
      "optionB":  "B: Super conductor",
      "optionC":  "C: Super computer",
      "optionD":  "D: Megaframe"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which gate is a single integrated circuit?",
      "answer":   "A: Gate",
      "optionA":  "A: Gate",
      "optionB":  "B: Mother Board",
      "optionC":  "C: Chip",
      "optionD":  "D: CPU"
    },
    {
      "question": "C is ____",
      "answer":   "A: A third generation high level language",
      "optionA":  "A: A third generation high level language",
      "optionB":  "B: A machine language",
      "optionC":  "C: An assembly language",
      "optionD":  "D: All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "Web pages are written using _____",
      "answer":   "C: HTML",
      "optionA":  "A: FTP",
      "optionB":  "B: HTTP",
      "optionC":  "C: HTML",
      "optionD":  "D: URL"
    },
    {
      "question": "The parity bit is added for the purpose of",
      "answer":   "B: Error detection",
      "optionA":  "A: Coding",
      "optionB":  "B: Error detection",
      "optionC":  "C: Controlling",
      "optionD":  "D: Indexing"
    },
    {
      "question": "India’s first super computer is ____",
      "answer":   "C: Param",
      "optionA":  "A: Agni",
      "optionB":  "B: Flow solver",
      "optionC":  "C: Param",
      "optionD":  "D: Trisul"
    },
    {
      "question": "The first movie released in 1982 with terrific computer animation and graphics was",
      "answer":   "A: Star wars",
      "optionA":  "A: Star wars",
      "optionB":  "B: Tron",
      "optionC":  "C: Forbidden planet",
      "optionD":  "D: Dark star"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which command combines the contents of one file with another?",
      "answer":   "C: APPEND",
      "optionA":  "A: RESTORE",
      "optionB":  "B: RENAME",
      "optionC":  "C: APPEND",
      "optionD":  "D: ADD"
    },

    {
      "question": "With which game is Geet Sethi associated?",
      "answer":   "D: Billiards",
      "optionA":  "A: Squash",
      "optionB":  "B: Kabbadi",
      "optionC":  "C: Lawn Tennis",
      "optionD":  "D: Billiards"
    },
    {
      "question": "Developed as a less strenuous alternative to basketball which game was invented in 1895 by William Morgan?",
      "answer":   "B: Volleyball",
      "optionA":  "A: Netball",
      "optionB":  "B: Volleyball",
      "optionC":  "C: Throwball",
      "optionD":  "D: Softball"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which sports is the participant called pugilist?",
      "answer":   "B: Boxing",
      "optionA":  "A: Sprinter",
      "optionB":  "B: Boxing",
      "optionC":  "C: Wrestling",
      "optionD":  "D: Javelin throw"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who finished 10th in the 2014/15 Premier League?",
      "answer":   "A: Crystal Palace",
      "optionA":  "A: Crystal Palace",
      "optionB":  "B: Stoke",
      "optionC":  "C: Everton",
      "optionD":  "D: West Ham"
    },
    {
      "question": "Track and field star Carl Lewis won how many gold medals at the 1984 Olympic games?",
      "answer":   "C: Four",
      "optionA":  "A: Two",
      "optionB":  "B: Three",
      "optionC":  "C: Four",
      "optionD":  "D: Eight"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which county did Ravi Shastri play for?",
      "answer":   "A: Glamorgan",
      "optionA":  "A: Glamorgan",
      "optionB":  "B: Leicestershire",
      "optionC":  "C: Gloucestershire",
      "optionD":  "D: Lancashire"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which two counties did Kapil Dev play?",
      "answer":   "A: Northamptonshire & Worcestershire",
      "optionA":  "A: Northamptonshire & Worcestershire",
      "optionB":  "B: Northamptonshire & Warwickshire",
      "optionC":  "C: Nottinghamshire & Worcestershire",
      "optionD":  "D: Nottinghamshire & Warwickshire"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who did Stone Cold Steve Austin wrestle at the 1998 edition of 'Over the Edge'?",
      "answer":   "C: Dude Love",
      "optionA":  "A: Cactus Jack",
      "optionB":  "B: Mankind",
      "optionC":  "C: Dude Love",
      "optionD":  "D: Mick Foley"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ricky Ponting is also known as what?",
      "answer":   "D: Punter",
      "optionA":  "A: The Rickster",
      "optionB":  "B: Ponts",
      "optionC":  "C: Ponter",
      "optionD":  "D: Punter"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long are professional Golf Tour players allotted per shot?",
      "answer":   "A: 45 seconds",
      "optionA":  "A: 45 seconds",
      "optionB":  "B: 25 seconds",
      "optionC":  "C: 1 minute",
      "optionD":  "D: 2 minutes"
    },

    {
      "question": "The isotope of uranium capable of sustaining chain reaction is",
      "answer":   "A: U-235",
      "optionA":  "A: U-235",
      "optionB":  "B: U-245",
      "optionC":  "C: U-239",
      "optionD":  "D: U-238"
    },
    {
      "question": "The age of most ancient geological formations is estimated by",
      "answer":   "D: Uranium - lead method",
      "optionA":  "A: Ra - Si method",
      "optionB":  "B: Potassium - argon method",
      "optionC":  "C: C14 method",
      "optionD":  "D: Uranium - lead method"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who suggested that most of the mass of the atom is located in the nucleus?",
      "answer":   "C: Rutherford",
      "optionA":  "A: Thompson",
      "optionB":  "B: Bohr",
      "optionC":  "C: Rutherford",
      "optionD":  "D: Einstein"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is/are the important raw material(s) required in cement industry?",
      "answer":   "C: Limestone and Clay",
      "optionA":  "A: Gypsum and Clay",
      "optionB":  "B: Clay",
      "optionC":  "C: Limestone and Clay",
      "optionD":  "D: Limestone"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of fire extinguisher is used for petroleum fire?",
      "answer":   "A: Powder type",
      "optionA":  "A: Powder type",
      "optionB":  "B: Liquid type",
      "optionC":  "C: Soda acid type",
      "optionD":  "D: Foam type"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is commonly called a 'polyamide'?",
      "answer":   "B: Nylon",
      "optionA":  "A: Terylene",
      "optionB":  "B: Nylon",
      "optionC":  "C: Rayon",
      "optionD":  "D: Orlon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Epoxy resins are used as",
      "answer":   "C: adhesives",
      "optionA":  "A: detergents",
      "optionB":  "B: insecticides",
      "optionC":  "C: adhesives",
      "optionD":  "D: moth repellents"
    },
    {
      "question": "Detergents used for cleaning clothes and utensils contain?",
      "answer":   "C: sulphonates",
      "optionA":  "A: bicarbonates",
      "optionB":  "B: bismuthates",
      "optionC":  "C: sulphonates",
      "optionD":  "D: nitrates"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is used for removing air bubbles from glass during its manufacture",
      "answer":   "A: Arsenous oxide",
      "optionA":  "A: Arsenous oxide",
      "optionB":  "B: Potassium carbonate",
      "optionC":  "C: Soda ash",
      "optionD":  "D: Feldspar"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a protein?",
      "answer":   "A: Natural rubber",
      "optionA":  "A: Natural rubber",
      "optionB":  "B: Starch",
      "optionC":  "C: Cellulose",
      "optionD":  "D: None of these"
    },

    {
      "question": "What do you do when you're tired ?",
      "answer":   "A: Rest",
      "optionA":  "A: Rest",
      "optionB":  "B: Bathe",
      "optionC":  "C: Watch",
      "optionD":  "D: Move"
    },
    {
      "question": "A child of my parents that is not my sister or my brother is my?",
      "answer":   "C: Self",
      "optionA":  "A: Uncle",
      "optionB":  "B: Sibling",
      "optionC":  "C: Self",
      "optionD":  "D: Shelve"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the soft do when the going is tough? Become",
      "answer":   "A: Tough",
      "optionA":  "A: Tough",
      "optionB":  "B: Shiverry",
      "optionC":  "C: Fast",
      "optionD":  "D: Hidden"
    },
    {
      "question": "What letter found after 'y' and before 'm' would spell a food?",
      "answer":   "A: A",
      "optionA":  "A: A",
      "optionB":  "B: B",
      "optionC":  "C: C",
      "optionD":  "D: D"
    },
    {
      "question": "When does the police sleep? When he's",
      "answer":   "A: Sleepy",
      "optionA":  "A: Sleepy",
      "optionB":  "B: Comes home",
      "optionC":  "C: Active",
      "optionD":  "D: Reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What disappears the moment it is talked about?",
      "answer":   "A: Silence",
      "optionA":  "A: Silence",
      "optionB":  "B: Rain",
      "optionC":  "C: Wind",
      "optionD":  "D: Thought"
    },
    {
      "question": "What goes round and comes around?",
      "answer":   "C: Choice",
      "optionA":  "A: The planet",
      "optionB":  "B: The moment",
      "optionC":  "C: Choice",
      "optionD":  "D: Time"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has a blade but doesn't rotate?",
      "answer":   "B: Razor",
      "optionA":  "A: Fan",
      "optionB":  "B: Razor",
      "optionC":  "C: Engine",
      "optionD":  "D: Disk drive"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has keys but no lock, space but no room?",
      "answer":   "B: Keyboard",
      "optionA":  "A: Door",
      "optionB":  "B: Keyboard",
      "optionC":  "C: Keyholes",
      "optionD":  "D: Key holder"
    },
    {
      "question": "The word has in it and it could feed in ears?",
      "answer":   "D: Bear",
      "optionA":  "A: Hear",
      "optionB":  "B: Monster",
      "optionC":  "C: Lion",
      "optionD":  "D: Bear"
    }




  ]
}